http://www.williamsparker.com/legal-notices

Toggle Menu
Alyssa L.
Counsel
Charles (Charlie) D.
Bailey, III
Partner
Charles (Dan) D.
Bailey, Jr.
Partner
Christina J.
Strasser
Associate
Colton F.
Castro
Associate
Diana L.
Berlin
Associate
Douglas J.
Partner
Elizabeth C.
Marshall
Partner
Elizabeth P.
Diaz
Partner
Elizabeth M.
Stamoulis
Partner
Fletcher H.
Rush
Associate
Gail E.
Partner
James L.
Counsel
Jeffrey A.
Grebe
Partner
Jeffrey T.
Partner
John L.
Moore
Partner
John T.
Berteau
Counsel
John C.
Attorney
Kimbrell J.
Hines
Counsel
Kyle D.
Partner
Mark A.
Schwartz
Partner
Michael J.
Wilson
Partner
Michele B.
Grimes
Counsel
Nicole A.
Behar
Counsel
Nicole F.
Christie
Associate
Patrick W.
Ryskamp
Partner
Peter T.
Partner
Rose-Anne B.
Frano
Partner
Steven D.
Counsel
Thomas J.
McLaughlin
Partner
Thomas B.
Luzier
Partner
Tommy E.
Gregory
Counsel
William M.
Seider
Partner
Zachary B.
Buffington
Partner
No results found, please search again.
HomeTeam
AttorneysProfessionals
Practices
Banking & FinanceBusiness SolutionsCorporateEstate Planning, Business Succession,
Estate & Trust AdministrationFiduciary ServicesHealthcare & Senior LivingIntellectual PropertyInternational Client ServicesLabor & EmploymentLitigationLand Use, Development & Local GovernmentReal EstateTax
Publications
BlogsRequisiteResource GuidesPractice Alerts & ArticlesGuest InterviewsPress RoomPresentations
The Firm
OverviewCommunityContactAwards, Rankings, & Certifications
Global ServicesCareers
Why Williams ParkerLawyersStaffLaw Students
Legal Notices Welcome to WilliamsParker.com. This website is operated by Williams, Parker, Harrison, Dietz & Getzen, PLLC. Please read these terms of use carefully before using this website. By using the website, you agree to be bound by these terms. We reserve the right to modify these terms at any time by posting modified terms, and your continued use of the website thereafter will constitute agreement with such modifications. Firm Organization. Williams, Parker, Harrison, Dietz & Getzen, PLLC, is a Florida professional limited liability company organized under Chapters 605 and 621, Florida Statutes. The company does business under the names “Williams Parker” and “Williams Parker Harrison Dietz & Getzen” pursuant to fictitious name registrations with the Florida Secretary of State. The company is referred to below and elsewhere on this website as either “Williams Parker” or “Williams Parker Harrison Dietz & Getzen.” Williams Parker is a wholly-owned subsidiary of Williams Parker Holdings, PLLC, a Florida professional limited liability company organized under Chapters 605 and 621, Florida Statutes. Williams Parker Holdings, PLLC, is owned by its members, all of whom are Williams Parker attorneys. Williams Parker attorneys designated on this website and elsewhere as “Partner” are members of Williams Parker Holdings, PLLC. Office. Williams Parker maintains its office at 200 South Orange Avenue, Sarasota, Florida 34236. Copyright Notice. © 2014-2020 Williams Parker Harrison Dietz & Getzen. All rights reserved. Unless otherwise indicated, Williams Parker owns the copyright and other rights in and to all content on this website, which includes (1) all text, graphics, sounds, information, and other materials, (2) the overall design and general look and feel of this website, as well as specific items, and (3) the particular and general selection, arrangement, and presentation of the content (even if certain items or information included in this website are in the public domain). Elements of this website are protected by trade dress, trademark, unfair competition, and other laws. You may reproduce the information on this website either solely for your personal use or for non-commercial distribution. Material reproduced from this website may not be modified, must be properly attributed, and must include the copyright notice which appears above.
Purpose of Website. The purpose of this website is to provide general information about Williams Parker to (1) our current clients, (2) persons interested in our qualifications and experience, and (3) law students and others who are considering a career with us. This website and its contents may be considered an advertisement or solicitation in some jurisdictions. However, this website is not intended to solicit clients or to provide legal advice.
No Attorney-Client Relationship. We welcome your inquiries and comments. Please feel free to call, write, or email us at any time. However, unless the information relates to a specific matter on which we already represent you under an existing attorney-client relationship, we will have no obligation to protect any information you convey to us. Until an attorney-client relationship is established, communication between us will not be privileged, may not be secure, and may be disclosed to other persons. Moreover, even if we already represent you in some matters, a conflict of interest or other reason could prevent us from representing you in a new or different matter. Therefore, you should not use this website to convey to us any confidential or sensitive information, even if you are a current client. In sum, any information we receive prior to a formal engagement with you on a specific matter will not be treated as confidential, secret, or protected. Compliance with Jurisdictional Requirements. We are unwilling to assume the representation of a client from any jurisdiction where that representation arises via a failure to comply with that jurisdiction’s restrictions on marketing materials, communications, or websites. No representation is made or intended that the quality of our legal services is greater than the quality of legal services provided by others. Prior results do not guarantee a similar outcome. Each representation has unique facts and circumstances that may impact results. Content Disclaimer. The content on this website is provided "as is." We do not represent the content is error-free, virus-free, or timely or that defects will be corrected. Neither Williams Parker nor any of our affiliates or employees make any representations regarding the timeliness, accuracy, or completeness of this website’s contents. We disclaim any liability or warranties, including any implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement. We disclaim any liability for your action or inaction in reliance on any of this website’s contents. Your sole remedy for any dissatisfaction with any of the website’s content is to refrain from using the website.
Links to Third-Party Resources. This website may contain links to other web pages or Internet sites. The links and the related entities are not under our control. The links are provided for your convenience only, and including them on our website does not constitute our endorsement of any linked entity or of the content, business practices, or privacy practices of any other websites. You acknowledge and agree your linking to, and using, any other website’s information through a link on our website is solely at your own risk.
Third-Party Advertisements and Pop-up Boxes. We do not allow advertising on our website. We neither authorize nor endorse any pop-up ad or other form of advertising which might appear while you are on our website.
No Uploading or Transmission. You may not upload to our website or transmit to us through this website (or by any other means) any material that is defamatory or obscene; that infringes any third party's copyrights, trademarks, or other proprietary rights; that violates any other rights of other parties; or that violates any law. Image Credits. Attorney photos, office photos, and other images which appear on this website are the property of, or licensed to, Williams Parker. Privacy Policy. We are committed to safeguarding your privacy. By using this website, including the submission to us of any personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, or phone number ("Personal Information"), you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.
Collection of Personal Information. Visiting the public areas of this website does not require you to provide any Personal Information. You may choose, however, to provide us Personal Information in order to contact us or to apply for a position at Williams Parker. The cookies used on the public areas of this website do not gather Personal Information, although your computer's browser may automatically provide us with certain other information such as the date and time of your visit, your computer's browser type, operating system and IP, and any referring and exiting URLs. Legally Required Disclosure. We may disclose any information, including Personal Information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request. Third Parties. Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell, rent, or transfer your Personal Information to third parties without your consent. We may, however, use the information you provide in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We may also collect, store, or accumulate certain non-Personal Information concerning use of this website, such as information regarding which of our webpages are most visited. We may retain other companies and individuals to perform on our behalf functions such as data analysis, webhosting, data storage, mass email communications, and hiring processes. Such third parties may be provided with access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions for us, but may not use such information for any other purpose. Such third parties may be located in countries that may not be subject to data protection laws similar to those prevailing in the jurisdiction in which such Personal Information is provided to, or received by, us. However, we require these third parties to adhere to procedures that are at least as restrictive as the procedures we follow ourselves with respect to your Personal Information, including this Privacy Policy. Links. The Williams Parker website may contain links to or from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from the Williams Parker website or otherwise visit. Changes to this Privacy Policy. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. The revised policy will also apply retroactively to all data we have collected through this website.
